Jhal Hello Hi
Guys Welcome to your own
Jo Hum As Investment In Hindi Mein
Kaise Aapke Today we will start this program with the
most popular segment
which keeps getting a lot of demand and that is
MK Jain Tausar Today it is very good for you to
bring you in this segment This is the area in which
I earned good profit in a WhatsApp message voice at very
cheap rates
Okay, I have done positional trading in it many times
and the interesting thing is this month I have
also sold one of its shares which is
going in good rates and the name of the stock is
ICICI Bank Result for Bank I have
subscribed to it so
in today's video we will talk about
what type of cutting of the first and second sides and what is the third
favorite we will talk about subscribe the
result is profit has
increased by 136 percent a rise of 366 percent
in profit has been seen and the
profit has increased to 2599 crores
around 600 whereas in the same quarter last
year the profit was double
this is the birth of 36 percent of profit  It was
good on zero basis, but one thing to
note is that within this quarter, what I said about profit,
one-off sales were made by two banks,
ICICI Lombard and ICICI
Prudential Life. Both have offices
added.
Now let's talk about net interest income. The
business of a bank is an interest business. The
bank gives loans to people and
charges interest. The bank
takes deposits from people. On one hand, it charges interest. On the
other hand,
if the subscription goes, it is net
interest income.
So, the net interest income of the bank has
increased by twenty percent on a fair and new year basis and has increased
from 900 to 1000 in this quarter. Whereas in the same quarter of
last year in June, the net interest income was
only 7733, which has now increased by 20% to
9280.
Now let's talk about net interest
margin. The net interest margin of the bank in this poster has been
That guest
point 6, when in any quarter last year the
net interest margin was 3.61, then
in this quarter the bank has
also shown an increase in the net interest margin on Airways.
However, if we compare the spider with the previous quarter
in Master, then the
net interest margin of Master was definitely higher,
that is 3.86,
that due to your report, the
bank has wisely created additional provisions
for cricket keeping this in mind
and that is
500, 500, Africa, Russia,
that they have provided this provident in the bank very
wisely on the basis of the principle of protection, that
in any situation, the
problems arising due to forward,
these factors can be easily taken care of on profit,
now John does it, keeping all these things
in mind, they have also created a good
amount of provision to keep the balance sheet strong.
Now let's talk about
non-performing assets, as you
know, the
discussion of the bank does not end without discussing net non-performing assets,
so they  In this quarter, the net NPA
i.e. non-performing assets and services has fallen
and has fallen to 1.3% whereas
in the previous quarter, which is 1.51% in the March quarter,
June quarter or March quarter,
it was 1.51%.
Along with this, the provision coverage ratio,
excluding technical light offs, has also increased to
786 points, whereas the master was
seventy-five point
that now the provisions,
after exploding the remaining 93 related provisions
and provision for tax, if we
talk about the remaining provisions, they have
fallen to 42 percent on hair on air basis and
in this poster, when the 204 four taxes were provided, then the
rate of provision provided was higher as per the last year's sheds.
Now, if we
believe the MD and CEO of the company, Sandeep Bakshi ji, then he says that the
IAS banker is continuously trying, is
continuously trying and has made a lot of progress.  He is
applying measures on this thing, my
friends,
ways to grow it, I will strengthen my balance sheet, let me tell you one thing, the bank
says that when its balance is
balance, then keep smiling, some
kind of people are appointed,
due to this Sandeep Bakshi ji says
that the bank is following a very systematic approach, regarding
asset quality and
provision management, the entire bank
is stressed on this thing and to do this thing well, the
bank is following a safe strategy, I am
telling you about 3 steps,
our Sandeep Bakshi told that the first
step is that the bank is constructing its portfolio in such a way,
sir, such a color
portfolio so that its balance becomes strong,
any kind of shock can be
easily tolerated, in this way it is
trying to build its balance sheet, it
tries to make it strong,
according to the number two step, it is preparing its pocket
base which is the base of operating profit in this
way, it is building it in a
systematic way and making it so that
any  If any kind of provision has to be
provided, then it can be provided
to Praveen easily and his profit base should be
soft on that and
in the third set,
according to Sandeep Bakshi ji,
ICICI Bank is working very proactively
for this thing that the
office robot is very strong on the balance of the bank
and any impact
of any provision on Arvind should be
recognized on the basis
of students, those
students mean that there should be a
systematic approach with understanding and it should be
shown, so
due to all these things, we see
that many brokerage houses,
many rating agencies which are listed, have
upgraded their rating on the bank, let's
talk about Edelweiss keyboard, apart from this,
earlier the target of the bank was given from 480 to
525 and talking about the target, CLSA is there,
CLSA had earlier given a target
of 480, they increased it to 500 and
clearly said  It is believed that the bank will perform better in the coming time
and perform means it will
perform well. Now we have normal good
performance and high flame. Due to this, both these
brokerage houses have to increase their target
price.
Apart from this, Sir Phase Loop System believes
that in the coming time, 0601 low holiday in
English believes that in the coming time, the
bank will perform well and they
too, who were
those unfaithful brothers, but why do brokerage houses have such a
view, let's discuss this a little. If we
talk about Edelweiss, Edelweiss
says that the point less which is on the table of the bank, the
point less which is on the bank is very
simple and because of this it does
not provide anything. If any
sudden loss or shock comes in this face, then it will
work as a shock absorber like a special vehicle. You have great
confidence that the bank's point less is above the point less
and if we talk about CLSA, then
while making its price advance, CLSA also made many decisions.
Share observations 20 They believe that
in the financial year 2022, the provision operating profit of the bank will
increase by 6 to 8 percent.
They also believe that the book value of the bank will
also increase by 6 to 8 percent.
Apart from this, two price targets were given.
While giving them, CLSA considered many things
like
they have considered a snippet of 7.5 percent for the
Sensex-21. Apart from this,
I have considered the five percent increase in Credit Kaushik. The
capital gain of Rs 3000 crore that the bank has made has also been considered. The
capital gain of Rs 12.5 thousand crore that the bank has made has
also been considered. So,
considering all the things,
CLSA believes that the price target should be
revised upward. They have
increased it from ₹480 to ₹500.
Apart from this, the
real estate also believes that the
reduction in the moratorium of the bank is
absolutely  There has been a reduction in expectations in this space as well.
Apart from this, the performance of the bank's provision for
operating profit is
very good. If we
compare it with its competitors, then no
competitor can break it. I am good but
call
a hot adult boy. Securities definitely
believes that asset quality may come under pressure
and this pressure may be
seen in the second half since another first half in 1122. Now we
will talk about brokerage houses that have upgraded it. The
reason behind this is that those who
subscribe and keeping the subscription in
mind, it
seems to me that it is believed that
they have cut it.
However, it is also believed that the
credit course will continue and
apart from this, the provision for will continue and will keep on being made. It will continue to get better. Whatever little
problem there is from America,
absolutely all things have ended, but
despite this, it is believed that the
balance of ICICI Bank will be
very good in the times to come.
Many list and brokerage houses believe that it will perform like this, the
details of which I will share with you right now. Let's
talk about the fundamentals of the bank.
So, look at the price
chart of the bank, the 52-week high of the bank is
Rs 552
and the 52-week low is Rs 268 and right now the price is
around Rs 361, which means it is moving towards a
52-week low. If we
keep an eye on this, we can look at the stock as per the opportunity.
Now let's talk about the market
capitalization of the bank. The market
capitalization is clearly Rs 2 lakh 34 thousand crore and the
market
capitalization is Rs 3000 crore, which means it is a fairly big
bank. Its price in English is 127
times on a channel basis and
23 times on a consolidated basis, whereas the
price of the industry is
around 20. According to me, the bank's price to book
value is quite attractive on a
standalone basis at 2.06 and 3 solid,
although it is even lower at 1.8, if you look at it  The
total volume on the machine shop that is being taken,
this share volume, in which the
CR that has happened in Tadoba is around two lakh 88
thousand crores, you can guess it is
around three crores, to
remove two crore 88 lakhs and approximately 3 pro
shares in the comment box and delivery delivery
is a clear indication of this, so why
many people have faith, they are
taking delivery,
now we were talking about the share holding
pattern in this, then you will be happy to know
that the advisor's view is
around four percent in this bank and the take of the instrument is
around 39%, the
stage of mutual fund within the deposit asset is around 28 percent of the
insurance company is around 50%
and half of the instrument is around six and a half days
and the children, you and I, non-institutional investors, the
state in this is around
seven and a half percent,
so son, this was my special presentation for you, in
which all the things were discussed, the quarterly results of ICICI Bank, what does the
CEO
and MD of this bank, Sandeep Bakshi ji, think,
what are the brokerage houses  What are you saying and
what is fundamental analysis? Yes, I have
also shared the details with you. I hope
you liked the video. If you liked the video, then
like the video and subscribe to my channel.
And if you want to become my member, then
press the join button along with subscribing. There are double
silver roadways and a platinum on all sides and I
want WhatsApp number. The phone number is in the description box.
You can call me and you
can join it. Apart from this, you have to
subscribe and you become the king of the market.